<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feature
      id="org.azzyzt.jee.mwe.magwien.feature"
      label="Azzyzt JEE modeling with entities, magwien version"
      version="1.2.3.qualifier"
      provider-name="azzyzt.org"
      plugin="org.azzyzt.jee.tools.mwe.projectgen.plugin">

   <description url="http://www.azzyzt.org">
      Azzyzt JEE Tools (magwien) is a collection of software tools
designed to assist software developers creating software using
Java Enterprise Edition 6. It is designed to be integrated into
popular Java IDEs.
   </description>

   <copyright url="http://www.wien.gv.at/english/">
      Copyright (c) 2011, Municipiality of Vienna, Austria
   </copyright>

   <license url="http://www.osor.eu/eupl">
      Licenses
--------

 Licensed under the EUPL, Version 1.1 or as soon they
 will be approved by the European Commission - subsequent
 versions of the EUPL (the &quot;Licence&quot;);
 You may not use this work except in compliance with the
 Licence.
 
 For convenience a plain text copy of the English version 
 of the Licence can be found in the file LICENCE.txt in
 the top-level directory of this software distribution.
 
 You may obtain a copy of the Licence in any of 22 European
 Languages at:

 http://www.osor.eu/eupl

 Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in
 writing, software distributed under the Licence is
 distributed on an &quot;AS IS&quot; basis,
 WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either
 express or implied.
 See the Licence for the specific language governing
 permissions and limitations under the Licence.


For the purpose of generating code, Azzyzt JEE Tools make use of and
bundles a copy of StringTemplate (http://www.stringtemplate.org/),
which is
 
 Copyright (c) 2008, Terence Parr
 All rights reserved.
 Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or 
 without modification, are permitted provided that the 
 following conditions are met:
 
 Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright 
 notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer.
 
 Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright 
 notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer in 
 the documentation and/or other materials provided with the distribution.
 
 Neither the name of the author nor the names of its contributors 
 may be used to endorse or promote products derived from this software 
 without specific prior written permission.
 
 THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY THE COPYRIGHT HOLDERS AND CONTRIBUTORS 
 &quot;AS IS&quot; AND ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT 
 LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS 
 FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE ARE DISCLAIMED. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE 
 COPYRIGHT OWNER OR CONTRIBUTORS BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, 
 INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING, 
 BUT NOT LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR SERVICES; 
 LOSS OF USE, DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER 
 CAUSED AND ON ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT 
 LIABILITY, OR TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) ARISING IN 
 ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE OF THIS SOFTWARE, EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE 
 POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.
   </license>

   <url>
      <update label="Azzyzt JEE Tools" url="http://azzyzt.manessinger.com/azzyzt_magwien/"/>
   </url>

   <plugin
         id="org.azzyzt.jee.runtime.site.magwien.fragment"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         fragment="true"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.azzyzt.jee.tools.mwe.projectgen.plugin"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.azzyzt.jee.tools.common.plugin"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.azzyzt.jee.tools.project"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

</feature>
